{"data":[{"question":"Besides rain, ________ is seldom pure.","a":"water naturally","b":"natural water","c":"water of nature","d":"the nature's water","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adjectives go before nouns that they modify","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"The FDA was set up in 1940 ________ that maintain standards for the sale of food and drugs.","a":"to enforce the laws","b":"to enforcing laws","c":"enforcing laws","d":"enforced the laws","answer":"1","explain":"\n+ Gerund: often used when actions are real, concrete or completed.\u00a0\n+ Infinitive: used when actions are unreal, abstract, or future.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"________ shops are closed on Saturday afternoon.","a":"Most the","b":"Most","c":"Most of","d":"Most our","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Most of + Pronoun\/ definite noun.\u00a0\n- Most + Noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"There are ________ organizations to help the deaf and the blind.","a":"much","b":"a little","c":"many","d":"little","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little\/ A lot of\/ a great deal of: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"________ electricity depends on a knowledge of atoms and the subatomic particles of which they are composed.","a":"The understanding","b":"To understand","c":"Understanding","d":"For understanding","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n+ Gerund: \u00a0used when actions are real, concrete or completed.\u00a0\n+ Infinitive: used when actions are unreal, abstract, or future.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"If England had not imposed a tax on tea two hundred and twenty years ago, ________ the United States have remained part of the British commonwealth?","a":"will","b":"would","c":"have","d":"had","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 3: If + past perfect, would\/could\/should + have + PP.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"Scientific fish farming, known as aquaculture, has existed for more than 4000 years, but scientists who ________ research in this field are only recently providing the kind of information that growers need to increase production.","a":"make","b":"makes","c":"does","d":"do","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Subject (scientists) is plural.\u00a0\n- Do research in.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"I paid ________ money for a new house.","a":"many","b":"a number of","c":"a large number of","d":"a lot of","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Many\/ a number of...+ countable noun.\u00a0\n- A lot of + uncountable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"A good summary should be ________ and ________.","a":"short \/ clear","b":"long \/ full of detail","c":"long \/ exciting","d":"short \/ lengthy","answer":"1","explain":"\n- short \/ clear: Is the most suitable in terms of meaning.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"},{"question":"Frank Lioyd Wright has been acclaimed by colleagues as ________ of all modern architects.","a":"the greater","b":"the greatest","c":"the more great","d":"the most great","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the superlative form of short adjective (great)\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"39","type":"1"}]}